Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Records WAG.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files
  - Subseries B: 1945-2004.
    - Bonding, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - "Cease and Desist": Correspondence, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Charges and Hearings: General, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Chicago: Midwest Advisory Board, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Office, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Children's Theatre, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Christmas and New Year's Greetings, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Colleges and Universities, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Committee: Ad Hoc Committee re: the 99-Seat Theatre Plan, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Committee: Ad Hoc Committee to meet with the Executive Secretary, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Committee: Advisory Committee on Chorus Affairs (ACCA), 1974 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Committee: Children's Theatre, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Committee: Constitutional Review, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Committee: Dinner Theatre, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Committee: Ethnic Minorities, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Committee: Film, Recording and Pay-TV, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Committee: Membership Education, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Committee: National Theatre, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Committee: National Theatre—Clippings, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Committee: National Theatre—Declaration of Intent and Supporting Correspondence, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Committee: President's Planning, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Committee: Production Contract, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Committee: Publications, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Committee: Repertory, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Committee: Re: Women, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Committee: Robeson, Paul Award, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Committee: Stage Managers, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - Committee: Stock, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - Committees: General, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Community Theatre, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - Constitutional Amendment: To Eliminate Junior/Senior Membership categories, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 38)
    - Contracts: Blank, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: Bicentennial, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence: Bikel, Theodore/President, undated (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence: deDiego, Frances V./Administrative Assistant Secretary, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence: Donahue, Vincent/Assistant Executive Secretary, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence: East West Players, Los Angeles, California, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence: Equity Members appearing at Bonfil's Theatre, Denver, Colorado, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence: General, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence: Genesee Valley Arts Foundation (GeVa) Employment of Aliens, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence: Grody, Donald/Executive Secretary, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence: Hewitt, Alan/Statistics, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence: Hoey, Randall Directing "Hair", 1974 (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence: Legal Department, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence: Magic Mountain Case, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence: Playhouse Theatre Reclassified as Off-Broadway, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence: Reimer, Walter/Business Representative, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence: Sucke, John/Business Representative, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence: Swire, Willard/Assistant Executive Secretary, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence: Warner, Jackie/On the Aisle, Inc., 1974 (Box 78, Folder 57)
    - Council, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 58)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Jack Golodner, Executive Secretary, Jan 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Jack Golodner, Executive Secretary, Jul 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - "Dear Councillor" Form Letters, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Defaulting Manager's List, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Deputy Meetings, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Dinner Theatre, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Dinner Theatre: American Dinner Theatre Institute (ADTI), 1974 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Dinner Theatre Negotiations, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Election Materials, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Energy Crisis, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Equal Opportunity Employment Commission, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Equity Library Theatre, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Establishment of a National Theatre, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Fact Finding Committee, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Foundation for the Extension and Development of the American Professional Theatre (FEDAPT), 1974 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Guest Artist Agreement, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Housing, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Industrial Shows, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - International [United States and Canada] Conference of Actors' Equity Association, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Jurisdiction, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Legislation: Golodner, Jack/Equity Legislative Representative, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Legitimate Theatre Tax Relief Fund, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Membership Meetings, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Membership Questionnaire: Started 1972, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 23A)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1974 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Nominating Committee, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - "Notice to Mediation Agencies" Re: Collective Bargaining Contracts, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Off-Broadway, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Off-Broadway: Negotiations, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - O'Neill, Eugene Memorial Theater Center, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Parts Breakdowns, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Pension and Welfare: Equity Trustee Portion Caucus, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Press Releases, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Production Contract: Negotiations, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Recommendations of Specifications for Architects and Builders in Construction of Theatres, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Safe and Sanitary Code: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Showcase, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Stock, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Stock: Council of Resident Stock Theatres (CORST), 1974 (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Stock: Negotiations, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - Theatre Authority, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - Theatre Authority: Jerry Lewis Labor Day MDAA Telethon, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - Theatre Authority: West Coast, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - Theatre by the Sea, Portsmouth, New Hampshire, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - Toronto: Canadian Autonomy, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 47)
    - Toronto: Charges and Hearings, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 48)
    - Toronto Office, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 49)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 50)
    - University Resident Theatre Association (URTA), 1974 (Box 79, Folder 51)
    - West Coast: California Arts Commission, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 52)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office, Jan 1974-May 1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office, Jun 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office Arbitrations, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office Charges and Hearings, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - West Coast: San Francisco Office, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - West Coast: Western Advisory Board, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - West Coast: Western Advisory Board Minutes, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - National Representation, 1974-2004 (Box 350)
    - Actors' Equity Foundation, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Agency: Franchises, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - American Theatre Association, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Artists, Composers and Authors Caucus, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Charges and Hearings, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Committee: Ad Hoc Committee Exploring the Question of the San Francisco Office, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Committee: Ad Hoc Committee Exploring the Question of the San Francisco Office Report, Dec 31, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Committee: Ethnic Minorities, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Committee: National Theatre, Jan 1975-Jul 1975 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Committee: National Theatre, Aug 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Committee: National Theatre—Clippings, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Committee: Publications, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Committee: Showcase Code, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Comprehensive Employment Training Act (CETA), 1975 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Bikel, Theodore/President, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Bikel, Theodore/President with the Central Committee of the Cultural Worker's Union, Moscow, USSR, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Grody, Donald/Executive Secretary, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Constitution and Minutes, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Jack Golodner, Executive Director, Jan 1975-Mar 1975 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Jack Golodner, Executive Director, Apr 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Jack Golodner, Executive Director, Sep 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Dinner Theatres, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Foundation for the Extension and Development of the Professional Theatre (FEDAPT), 1975 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Foundation Giving to Theatres, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Housing, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - National Committee for Cultural Resources, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - National Conference, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA), 1975 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Special Membership Meeting Re: Musicians' Strike (Transcript), Sep 23, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Toronto: Canadian Autonomy, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - West Coast: California Arts Commission, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles 99-Seat Theatre Plan, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Actors' Equity Foundation, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Actors' Fund, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Agency: Franchises, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Agency: General, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Aliens, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting, Apr 9, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Arbitrations, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Auditions and Interviews, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - "Cease and Desist" Correspondence, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Chicago: Midwest Advisory Board, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Office, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Colleges and Universities, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Committee: Ad Hoc Committee Exploring the Question of the San Francisco Office, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Committee: Advisory Committee on Chorus Affairs (ACCA), 1976 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Committee: Dinner Theatre, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Committee: Ethnic Minorities, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Committee: Film, Recording and Pay-TV, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Committee: Membership Education, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Committee: National Theatre, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Committee: Off-Broadway, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Committee: Publications, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Committee: Repertory Theatres (LORT), 1976 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Committee: Re: Women, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Committee: Showcase, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Committee: Stock, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Committees: General, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Community Theatre, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Contracts: Blank, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence:: Bikel, Theodore/President, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence: Claims, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence: Donahue, Vincent Memorial Fund, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: Fields, Lillian re: Health Plan Problems, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence: General, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence: Grody, Donald/Executive Secretary, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence: Hewitt, Alan/Statistics, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence: Kattwinkel, Walter/Business Representative, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence: Legal Department, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence: Members appearing without contract in "Women Behind Bars", 1976 (Box 81, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence: Michaels, Scott and South Pacific Productions, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence: Music Fair Enterprises, Inc., 1976 (Box 81, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence: Non-Union Continental Theatre Company, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Non-Union Tour of "Hair", 1976 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Reimer, Walter/Business Representative, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Slaughter, Harriet/Chief Representative, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Swire, Willard/Assistant Executive Secretary, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: "The Insect Comedy", 1976 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Vigliano, Barbara/Business Representative, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Council, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Council: Letters for Council Action/Executive Action, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Council: Special Order of Business re: a discussion of Cooperatives, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Jack Golodner, Executive Director, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Minutes, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Cuts Board, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - "Dear Councillor" Form Letters, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Defaulting Managers' List, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Deputy Meetings, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Dinner Theatres, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Dinner Theatres: American Dinner Theatre Institute (ADTI), 1976 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Election Materials, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Equity Library Theatre, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Foundation for the Extension and Development of the Professional Theatre (FEDAPT), 1976 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Fuldheim Theatre, Cleveland, Ohio, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Guest Artist Agreement, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza, Jul 1976-Oct 1976 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza, Nov 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Housing: Press Clippings, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Industrial Shows, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Jurisdiction, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Jurisdiction: "Bunnies '76" Playboy Club, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Jurisdiction: Busch Gardens, Williamsburg, Virginia "Ghosts of the Globe", 1976 (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Kani, John and Ntshona, Winston Jailed in South Africa: Protest, Correspondence and Clippings, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Legitimate Theatre Tax Relief Fund, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Massachusetts Center Repertory Company, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Membership Meetings, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - New Arts Theatre Company, Dallas, Texas, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA), 1976 (Box 82, Folder 37)
    - Nominating Committee, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 38)
    - Off-Broadway, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 39)
    - Off-Off-Broadway, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 40)
    - O'Neill, Eugene Theater Center, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 41)
    - Parts Breakdowns, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 42)
    - Pension and Welfare, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 43)
    - Pension and Welfare: Equity Portion Trustee Caucus, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 44)
    - Producer's Association of Children's Theatre (PACT), 1976 (Box 82, Folder 45)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 46)
    - Safe and Sanitary Code, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 47)
    - Showcase Code, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 48)
    - Stock: Council of Resident Stock Theatres (CORST), 1976 (Box 82, Folder 49)
    - Stock: Council of Stock Theatres (COST), 1976 (Box 82, Folder 50)
    - Theatre Authority, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 51)
    - Theatre for Young Audiences (TYA) Contract, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Toronto: Canadian Actors' Equity Association, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Toronto: Canadian Autonomy, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - West Coast: California Arts Commission, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles 99-Seat Theatre Plan, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - West Coast: San Francisco Office, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - West Coast: Western Advisory Board Minutes, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Agency: Franchises, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Agency: General, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Agency: International Creative Management (ICM) Ben Gazzara re: Commission, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Aliens, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Bayfield, St. Clair Award, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Committee: Ethnic Minorities, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Committee: National Theatre, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Committee: Publications, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Comprehensive Employment Training Act (CETA), 1977 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Concerned Citizens for the Arts of New York State, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Bikel, Theodore/President, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Hewitt, Alan/Statistics, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 21A)
    - Council, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Council: Letters for Council Action/Executive Action, Jan 1977-Jul 1977 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Council: Letters for Council Action/Executive Action, Aug 1977-Nov 1977 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees (CPE): Jack Golodner, Executive Director (Changes to Department for Professional Employees in December), 1977 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Department for Professional Employees, AFL-CIO: Jack Golodner, Director (Formerly Council for Professional Employees-CPE), 1977 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Equity Library Theatre: Production and Inventory Lists, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Foundation for the Extension and Development of the Professional Theatre (FEDAPT), 1977 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Form Letters, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 28A)
    - Housing: Committee, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza, Jan 1977-Feb 1977 (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza, Mar 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza Board of Estimate Hearings, Feb 3, 1977-Feb 4, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza Press and Clippings, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts Repertory Company, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - National Council for Arts and Educations, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA), 1977 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Production Contract, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Toronto: Canadian Autonomy, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Conflict of Interest Charges and the 99-Seat Theatre Plan, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles 99-Seat Theatre Plan, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles 99-Seat Theatre Plan Member Petitions, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - West Coast: Membership Meetings, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Agency: Franchises, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Agency: General, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Bayfield, St. Clair Award, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - British American Repertory Company, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Chicago: Midwest Advisory Board, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Committee: Film, Recording and Pay-TV, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Committee: National Theatre, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Committee: Publications, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Bikel, Theodore/President, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Grody, Donald/Executive Secretary, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Council: Letters for Council Action/Executive Action, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - "Count Your Blessings" Professional Theatre Employment by Alan Hewitt, Mar 1978 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Department of Professional Employees, AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - National Commission for Manpower Policy, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - National Council for Arts and Education, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 33)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 34)
    - Off Off Broadway, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Redgrave, Vanessa: Bikel Correspondence and Press Clippings, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - West Coast: California Arts Council, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - West Coast: California Confederation of the Arts, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - West Coast: National Endowment for the Arts Issues, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - West Coast: San Francisco Subsidiary Rights Agreements, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Agency: Franchises, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Agency: General, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - American Stage Magazine, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Bayfield, St. Clair Award, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Chicago: Midwest Advisory Board, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Committee: Film, Recording and Pay-TV, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Committee: National Theatre, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Committee: Professional Study Program, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Committee: Publications/Editorial Board, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Committees: General, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Bikel, Theodore/President, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: General, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Loveman, Lenore/Director of Membership Education and Communication, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Southern Arizona Light Opera Company, Tucson, Arizona, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Council, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Department of Professional Employees, AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Handbook, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Hotline: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Hotline Scripts, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Housing: Lease Rider Definition, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Housing: Manhattan Plaza, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - Labor Institute for Human Enrichment: Jack Golodner /Executive Director, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - Legislation, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 32)